<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Glasgow Azure User Group</title>
    <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Glasgow Azure User Group</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/courses/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/publication/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/slides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2017&#34;&gt;2017&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On August 23rd 2017, a group of engaged and enthusiastic IT professions gathered at the HAYS Recruitment in the City Centre of Glasgow.  We had two Microsoft experts as speakers cover the basics of Azure and also what serverless within the platform means.  If you didn&amp;rsquo;t managed to attend the event it was recorded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/3514904&#34; title=&#34;Little red riding hood - Click to Watch!&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/7YTMFQp.png&#34; alt=&#34;Little red ridning hood&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On the 25th October 2017, our meetup focused on Security.  We had three speakers cover everything from native Azure security products to third party products.  There was also a session that cover HoloLens and virtual reality.   The session was recorded and is available via YouTube&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/3514904&#34; title=&#34;Little red riding hood - Click to Watch!&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/7YTMFQp.png&#34; alt=&#34;Little red ridning hood&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On the 6th December 2017, we had MVP Ed Baker take us through the latest cloud solutions available for sharing files within your organisation and Microsoft employee Stephen Armory spoke about the data platforms available within Azure.  The session was recorded and is available via YouTube&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/3514904&#34; title=&#34;Little red riding hood - Click to Watch!&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/7YTMFQp.png&#34; alt=&#34;Little red ridning hood&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2018&#34;&gt;2018&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We held our February 2018 meetup on the 21st where Simon Binder and Gary Lumsden spoke to us:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At our April 25th 2018 meetup we had David McKay take us through an Introduction to Docker and we had Andrew Kemp come along and share his Office 365 knowledge.  The session was recorded and is available via YouTube at:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;June 2018 meetup saw two Microsoft employees visit and speak to use regarding Data Centre Transformations and Cognitive Services &amp;amp; Bots.  Unfortunately this meetup wasn&amp;rsquo;t filmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At our August 2018 meetup we had our sponsors F5 talk about their products and how they can be used within the Cloud and we also had another sponsor, Servent give us details on how they&amp;rsquo;ve implemented Azure at a customer and share the real life journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our October 2018 meetup was held as a Super meetup in conjunction with the Glasgow SQL User Group and Scottish PowerShell and DevOps Group.  We have five speakers give us lightning talks on various different subjects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In December 2018, we had two Swedish MVP&amp;rsquo;s attend, Simon Binder and Alexander Ardvisson.  &lt;em&gt;Unfortunately this meetup wasn&amp;rsquo;t recorded.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2019&#34;&gt;2019&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With our first meetup of 2019 in February we welcomed Scott Tees, from Police Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Safe Communities Unit and also Justin Black from HAYS who shared information about the current job market in Glasgow and Edinburgh. &lt;strong&gt;Unfortunately this meetup wasn&amp;rsquo;t recorded.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In April, we saw Ryan Yates visit our meetup and deliver a mammoth session entitled &amp;ldquo;Using Azure DevOps, ARM Templates and Terraform for standing up Dev &amp;amp; Test Infrastructure in Azure&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2020&#34;&gt;2020&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In February we saw &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/janet-moss-41737720/&#34;&gt;Janet Moss&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-mcinnes-7b774b75/&#34;&gt;Chris McInnes&lt;/a&gt; present a session entitled &amp;ldquo;50 Ways to Kill Your Project Manager&amp;rdquo; and we also had Michael Stephenson present &amp;ldquo;Building awesome Serverless Solutions with Terraform and Azure&amp;rdquo;. &lt;em&gt;Unfortunately this meetup wasn&amp;rsquo;t recorded.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In April, we held our first virtual meetup and we had &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/gary-hay-0b312623/&#34;&gt;Gary Hay&lt;/a&gt; present a session on Azure Sentinel. &lt;em&gt;Unfortunately this meetup wasn&amp;rsquo;t recorded.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In June, we held our second virtual meetup and had &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/azureapril/&#34;&gt;April Edwards&lt;/a&gt; present a session on &amp;ldquo;Storing Data in Azure&amp;rdquo;.  And we also had &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ricastle/&#34;&gt;Richard Castle&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/mark-boddington/&#34;&gt;Mark Boddington&lt;/a&gt; from F5 talk about NGINX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/conduct/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;code-of-conduct&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This code of conduct outlines our expectations for participants within the Glasgow Azure User Group community, as well as steps to reporting unacceptable behaviour. We are committed to providing a welcoming and inspiring community for all and expect our code of conduct to be honoured. Anyone who violates this code of conduct may be banned from the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are dedicated to providing a harassment-free user group/conference experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, age or religion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our aim is to foster a community that is open to all and strives to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be friendly and patient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be welcoming: We strive to be a community that welcomes and supports people of all backgrounds and identities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be considerate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be respectful: You may not agree with each other all the time but disagreement is no excuse for poor behaviour and poor manners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;reporting-process&#34;&gt;Reporting Process&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you experience or witness unacceptable behaviour—or have any other concerns—please report it by contacting us via one of these methods:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:conduct@gaug.co.uk&#34;&gt;conduct@gaug.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In person while at an event - please ask to speak to a committee member.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;consequences-of-unacceptable-behaviour&#34;&gt;Consequences of Unacceptable Behaviour&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unacceptable behaviour from any community member, including sponsors and those with decision-making authority, will not be tolerated. Anyone asked to stop unacceptable behaviour is expected to comply immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a community member engages in unacceptable behaviour, the community organisers may take any action they deem appropriate, up to and including a temporary ban or permanent expulsion from the community without warning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not tolerate harassment of participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any conference venue, including talks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees or speakers violating these rules will be asked to leave the meeting, and will be refused entrance to future meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-information&#34;&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are being harassed, notice that someone else is being harassed, or have any other concerns, please contact a member of organising staff.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;sponsors&#34;&gt;Sponsors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to working with the following partners to bring you the Glasgow Azure User Group events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Sponsors&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hays.co.uk&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/img/hays.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Hays&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Hays is the leading global specialist recruitment group, and the market leader in places such as the UK, Germany and Australia. They are the experts in recruiting qualified, professional and skilled people across a wide range of specialised industries and professions.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://incrementalgroup.co.uk/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/img/incrementalgroup.png&#34; alt=&#34;Incremental Group&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Incremental Group are a leading Microsoft Dynamics (AX, NAV and CRM) and Dynamics 365 partner with a wide range of services including Azure, Data Science and Power BI.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.servent.co.uk/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/img/servent.png&#34; alt=&#34;Servent&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Servent are a Microsoft Cloud consultancy and Microsoft Gold Cloud Platform partner helping cloud-power large enterprises.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.f5.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/img/f5.png&#34; alt=&#34;F5&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;F5 Networks specialize in application delivery networking (ADN) technology for the delivery of web applications and the security, performance, availability of servers, data storage devices, and other network and cloud resources.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nginx.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/img/nginx.png&#34; alt=&#34;NGINX&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NGINX, now a part of F5, Inc., is the company behind the popular open source project, NGINX. We offer a suite of technologies for developing and delivering modern applications. Together with F5, our combined solution bridges the gap between NetOps and DevOps, with multi cloud application services that span from code to customer.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.shapesecurity.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ashy-hill-052747203.azurestaticapps.net/img/shape.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Shape Security&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shape Security, based in Santa Clara, CA, defends the world&amp;rsquo;s largest enterprises from all types of fraud against their online applications. Shape&amp;rsquo;s fraud prevention platform detects and blocks up to 2 billion fraudulent or unwanted transactions daily, while keeping 200 million legitimate human logins and other interactions safe. Shape provides omnichannel protection for web applications, mobile applications and API interfaces; the company&amp;rsquo;s mobile SDK is deployed on more than 200 million iOS and Android devices worldwide. Shape Security is now a part of F5 Networks. F5 and Shape have joined forces to defend every application against attacks, fraud, and abuse in a multi-cloud world.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
